[{"answer": "So, hows your week going", "docId": "01-03", "aSentId": 15, "question": "", "qSentId": 14},{"answer": " Oh, its been a nightmare!  Its been so busy, and the search for a ne", "docId": "01-03", "aSentId": 16, "question": "So, hows your week going", "qSentId": 15},{"answer": " Oh, Im sorry to hear that.  Whats happening with the search?  Are you no", "docId": "01-03", "aSentId": 20, "question": " Oh, its been a nightmare!  Its been so busy, and the search for a ne", "qSentId": 19},{"answer": "No, its not that.  Plenty of people have applied", "docId": "01-03", "aSentId": 24, "question": " Oh, Im sorry to hear that.  Whats happening with the search?  Are you no", "qSentId": 23},{"answer": " Whats the problem then", "docId": "01-03", "aSentId": 25, "question": "No, its not that.  Plenty of people have applied", "qSentId": 24},{"answer": " Well, Ive only received a few decent resumes.  The rest are terrible", "docId": "01-03", "aSentId": 26, "question": " Whats the problem then", "qSentId": 25},{"answer": " Really", "docId": "01-03", "aSentId": 27, "question": " Well, Ive only received a few decent resumes.  The rest are terrible", "qSentId": 26},{"answer": " Yes.  Let me show you some of them", "docId": "01-03", "aSentId": 28, "question": " Really", "qSentId": 27},{"answer": " OK", "docId": "01-03", "aSentId": 32, "question": " Yes.  Let me show you some of them", "qSentId": 31},{"answer": " Look at this one, for example.  It looks so unprofessional.  Theres no heading", "docId": "01-03", "aSentId": 33, "question": " OK", "qSentId": 32},{"answer": " It does look bad.  Its so easy to create a professional looking resume.  Ther", "docId": "01-03", "aSentId": 37, "question": " Look at this one, for example.  It looks so unprofessional.  Theres no heading", "qSentId": 36},{"answer": " I know.  This resume just makes me think that the applicant is unprofessiona", "docId": "01-03", "aSentId": 41, "question": " It does look bad.  Its so easy to create a professional looking resume.  Ther", "qSentId": 40},{"answer": " I know.  I wouldnt either", "docId": "01-03", "aSentId": 45, "question": " I know.  This resume just makes me think that the applicant is unprofessiona", "qSentId": 44},{"answer": " And look at this one.  Were hiring for a secretary, right", "docId": "01-03", "aSentId": 46, "question": " I know.  I wouldnt either", "qSentId": 45},{"answer": " Yea", "docId": "01-03", "aSentId": 47, "question": " And look at this one.  Were hiring for a secretary, right", "qSentId": 46},{"answer": " Well, this applicants objective says, To secure a position as an intern at ", "docId": "01-03", "aSentId": 48, "question": " Yea", "qSentId": 47},{"answer": " They couldnt even be bothered to write an objective thats specific to the jo", "docId": "01-03", "aSentId": 50, "question": " Well, this applicants objective says, To secure a position as an intern at ", "qSentId": 49},{"answer": " I guess not.  Some applicants dont take the time to tailor their application", "docId": "01-03", "aSentId": 56, "question": " They couldnt even be bothered to write an objective thats specific to the jo", "qSentId": 55},{"answer": " Youre right.  I guess you dont want to hire a person that sends in that kind o", "docId": "01-03", "aSentId": 61, "question": " I guess not.  Some applicants dont take the time to tailor their application", "qSentId": 60},{"answer": " Right.  I wouldnt.  If they cant even spend the time to make a good resume", "docId": "01-03", "aSentId": 65, "question": " Youre right.  I guess you dont want to hire a person that sends in that kind o", "qSentId": 64},{"answer": " They probably wouldnt be a very good employee", "docId": "01-03", "aSentId": 69, "question": " Right.  I wouldnt.  If they cant even spend the time to make a good resume", "qSentId": 68},{"answer": "Oh, look at this one too.  Its full of errors.  Read the first few lines", "docId": "01-03", "aSentId": 70, "question": " They probably wouldnt be a very good employee", "qSentId": 69},{"answer": " Wow!  They misspelled so many words", "docId": "01-03", "aSentId": 71, "question": "Oh, look at this one too.  Its full of errors.  Read the first few lines", "qSentId": 70},{"answer": " I know.  Theres no excuse for that.  That creates a terrible first impression", "docId": "01-03", "aSentId": 72, "question": " Wow!  They misspelled so many words", "qSentId": 71},{"answer": " Youd think someone would take the time to spell check things", "docId": "01-03", "aSentId": 76, "question": " I know.  Theres no excuse for that.  That creates a terrible first impression", "qSentId": 75},{"answer": " Youd think.  OK, let me show you one more.  Check this one out", "docId": "01-03", "aSentId": 77, "question": " Youd think someone would take the time to spell check things", "qSentId": 76},{"answer": " Is that one resume", "docId": "01-03", "aSentId": 81, "question": " Youd think.  OK, let me show you one more.  Check this one out", "qSentId": 80},{"answer": " Yes!  Its 20 pages.  Its way too long.  I dont even have the time to read it, s", "docId": "01-03", "aSentId": 82, "question": " Is that one resume", "qSentId": 81},{"answer": " Thats way too wordy.  A resume should be brief, like 1-4 pages", "docId": "01-03", "aSentId": 86, "question": " Yes!  Its 20 pages.  Its way too long.  I dont even have the time to read it, s", "qSentId": 85},{"answer": " I know.  This person wrote down way too many details", "docId": "01-03", "aSentId": 87, "question": " Thats way too wordy.  A resume should be brief, like 1-4 pages", "qSentId": 86},{"answer": " I didnt realize that so many people were clueless when it comes to resumes", "docId": "01-03", "aSentId": 88, "question": " I know.  This person wrote down way too many details", "qSentId": 87},{"answer": " Based on the resumes Ive received, it seems like a lot of people are", "docId": "01-03", "aSentId": 89, "question": " I didnt realize that so many people were clueless when it comes to resumes", "qSentId": 88},{"answer": " Well, Im sorry youre having such a hard time finding a good applicant", "docId": "01-03", "aSentId": 90, "question": " Based on the resumes Ive received, it seems like a lot of people are", "qSentId": 89},{"answer": " Thanks for listening.  Ive got another pile of resumes to look through, s", "docId": "01-03", "aSentId": 91, "question": " Well, Im sorry youre having such a hard time finding a good applicant", "qSentId": 90},{"answer": " Good luck", "docId": "01-03", "aSentId": 95, "question": " Thanks for listening.  Ive got another pile of resumes to look through, s", "qSentId": 94}]
